Taras Shmilyk

CONTACT

Lviv, Ukraine

E-mail: taras.shmilyk@gmail.com

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/taras-

shmilyk-7b438b164/

Phone: +380500614124

SUMMARY

I am a Computer Science student who's really interested in design (graphic/UI/UX) and likes to actively participate in the process. I am ready to take on interesting and challenging tasks to deepen my knowledge and gain valuable experience. Personal portfolio: https://shmilyk-ph.com.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance

July 2018 — Present

Graphic Designer

- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom; Figma
- Content creation (logos, visuals)
- Photo retouching & editing
- Real Estate market research
- Photography sessions (portraits, landscapes, gatherings, celebrations, story filming)

Jeppesen, A Boeing Company (Gdansk, Poland)

July 2019 — August 2019

R&D Intern

Member of a blockchain research project

- Blockchain market & business research
- Creation of Hyperledger blockchain microproject (using python3, Hyperledger Fabric, Hyperledger Composer, docker, docker-compose, Yeoman & composer-rest-server on Linux)
- Brainstorming sessions, read-outs and tech-talks
- Box, Confluence, Taiga

EDUCATION

Artificial Intelligence (Computer Science, Bachelor's Degree)

September 2017 — July 2021

Lviv Polytechnic National University

- Python Chat-bot Project:
- python3 + tkinter
- Drone Flight Planner Project:
- python 2.7 + dronekit-sitl
- Embedded Linux (Raspberry Pi + Raspbian)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

python3: Flask + HTML/CSS, Pandas, NumPY, Matplotlib; OOP, SOLID. Microprojects:

- Flask Text Handler
- A front (HTML/CSS) + back (Flask, re) server that handles text input
- Travis CI integration (unittest)
- Windows/Linux hosting
- Custom error handling

Taras Shmilyk

 FolderCrawler - A script (using python os module) to crawl through numerous subdirectories and delete only necessary files inside
SQL, NoSQL Databases
Git, Github
Docker, Virtualbox
Travis, Jenkins, Semaphore CI/CD; Confluence

LANGUAGES

Upper Intermediate/Advanced English Advanced Russian Elementary German

INTERESTS

Souls-Like Games, Metro 2033 Universe, Resident Evil, Warhammer 40k, WoW/Hearthstone, Heroes of Might & Magic Retrowave/Cyberpunk/Mecha manga

Taras Shmilyk 2